SALAMI ABIODUN

Gbagada Lagos | +2348154224416 | Salamabiodun01@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Deadline-driven Graphic Designer focused on overseeing projects from concept through final delivery. Successfully creates brand messages, strategies and key graphic productions. Resourceful and hardworking with vendor sourcing expertise and empowering leadership skills illustrated over 5 years of industry success. Creative Graphic Designer with talent for developing unique custom artwork. Innovative approach to ideas and concept development. Offering 5 years of expertise overseeing individual projects and brand development.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- PC and Mac platforms
- Photography composition
- Logo design
- Digital design
- Branding strategies
- Digital imagery
- Graphic design

- Production layouts
- Website graphics
- Visual design
- Image manipulation
- Illustration
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Critical Thinking

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

BOOK24.NG

GRAPHICS/VISUAL DESIGNER

2021-Present

- Created digital image files for use in digital and traditional printing methods.
- Completed final touches for projects before rollout.
- Contributed design ideas in early planning stages with customers and project managers.
- Developed display, marketing, and packaging materials to support product branding strategies.
- Applied knowledge of production to create high-quality images.
- Put together videos for social media, advertising, and informational purposes.
- Designed creative digital displays used in online advertising for local businesses.

TEESAS EDUCATIONAL SERVICES

VISUAL FX/MOTION GRAPHICS DESIGNER

2019-2021

- Met challenging demands of productions by developing cutting-edge effects.
- Developed new rigs to better meet demands of Video productions.
- Brainstormed new designs and techniques through close work with both technical and non-technical personnel.
- Managed edits in close collaboration with editing team and incorporated required changes into updated designs.
- Prepared digital storyboards outlining creative progression of projects.
- Advanced designs from concept toward implementation by creating mock-ups for review.

EDUCATION

Polytechnic Ibadan (HND) Electrical Electronics 2013-2017

PROFESSIONAL TOOLS

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP | ADOBE PREMIER PRO | CANVA | FIGMA | HTML5 | CSS 3

REFERENCE

Available on request